<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tips>
    <tip>
        <title>Dempsey Roll</title>
        <description>The Dempsey Roll is a powerful combination of head movement and body rotation, popularized by Jack Dempsey. It allows the boxer to throw powerful hooks while evading punches.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Corkscrew Punch</title>
        <description>The Corkscrew Punch, developed by Jack Johnson, involves rotating the fist during a punch to increase power and penetration. It's especially effective in close-range fighting.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Left Hook to the Body</title>
        <description>The left hook to the body is a devastating punch aimed at the opponent’s ribs or liver. It can knock the wind out of them and set up other punches.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Uppercut</title>
        <description>The uppercut is a rising punch aimed at the chin or body. It’s especially effective when delivered from close range and can knock out an opponent if landed cleanly.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Right Cross</title>
        <description>The right cross is a powerful straight punch that comes from the rear hand. It is a key punch in a boxer’s arsenal, often following a jab to set up a knockout blow.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Slip and Counter</title>
        <description>Slipping punches and then countering with a punch of your own is a crucial defensive technique. It involves moving your head off the centerline to avoid a punch while being in position to retaliate.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Philly Shell</title>
        <description>The Philly Shell is a defensive stance popularized by Floyd Mayweather. It involves using the shoulder to block punches while positioning the hand for quick counters.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Double Jab</title>
        <description>The double jab is an effective offensive move where the boxer throws two quick jabs in succession. This helps to control the distance and set up other punches.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Check Hook</title>
        <description>The check hook is a defensive move used to counter an aggressive opponent by pivoting and landing a quick hook while moving backward.</description>
    </tip>
    <tip>
        <title>Overhand Right</title>
        <description>The overhand right is a punch thrown at an angle, coming down over the top of the opponent's guard. It's useful for landing power punches over an opponent's jab.</description>
    </tip>
</tips>
